Rudenko Vyacheslav

Frontend developer with a passion for creating engaging and user-friendly web experiences.

Location: Kyiv, Ukraine Mobile: +380953889372

Email: rudenkoslava787@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/vyacheslav-rudenko-310809270

GitHub: github.com/Slava-11

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I have worked for two years in various companies doing blogs, email newsletters I can do responsive layout know many interesting techniques such as: color theme, animation and more. I am a hard worker, meet deadlines and can work with extra tasks.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Mamontovadesign | Frontend Developer May 2022 - Present | Kyiv, Ukraine

- Unfortunately, I signed a non-disclosure agreement, so I am unable to disclose any information.
- At this job, I utilized skills such as Sass, JavaScript,
 Vite, and MJML for email template development.

Etcetera Agency | Frontend Developer May 2021 - Apr 2022 | Kyiv, Ukraine

- During my time at Etcetera Agency, I primarily focused on front-end development, including the creation of over 25 responsive pages with engaging animations, all built using BEM methodology.
- On this job, I utilized skills in Sass, JavaScript, Vite, and animation.

SKILLS

Programming Languages

- Proficient in: HTML, CSS, SASS, JS, MJML.
- Working knowledge of: Visual Studio Code, responsive layout, lite and dark mode, animation, BEM, Vite.

EDUCATION

Degree Name

KPI, September 2020 - Present

PROJECTS

KPI.ua | Role Frontend developer

- Implemented and maintained a large-scale codebase to develop a web application consisting of 30 pages.
 Optimized website performance resulting in a 30% increase in overall efficiency.
- I have utilized various technologies such as Sass,
 JavaScript and Vite to build features on projects. All my work has been developed using the BEM methodology to ensure clean and scalable code.

Ibis online store. | Role Frontend developer

- On this project, I worked on over 40 fully responsive pages for the Ibis website. I implemented unique and engaging animations using cutting-edge technologies such as Vite. In addition, I created various components such as a product catalog, slider, burger menu, and more. As a result of these efforts, the website's effectiveness increased by 15%.
- I utilized technologies such as Sass, JS, and Vite to build website features, and also implemented animations on websites. In addition, I designed and coded email templates using the MJML framework.

<u>Dnipro-m online store.</u> | Role Frontend developer

- I introduced my fresh ideas that made the website more visually appealing with animations, blazing fast, and ranked high in search engines. As a result, I boosted the website's effectiveness by 20%.
- I utilized cutting-edge technologies such as Sass, JS, and Vite to bring animations to life on the website.

AWARDS AND ACCOLADES

IT Academy

 Completed IT Academy courses on web development fundamentals including HTML, CSS, and JavaScript.
 Built several responsive and dynamic web applications using popular front-end frameworks such as Vite. Graduated with strong proficiency in frontend technologies and software engineering principles.